<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sergio Bertolín</title><link>https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sergio Bertolín</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:34:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to make gradle build to fail hard when parameters are not correct</title><link>https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/blogpost3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:34:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/blogpost3/</guid><description>Gradle is a build tool widely spread in java projects. It is quite complex inside but it seems easy to make a build.gradle to prepare our project to gather dependencies and run it.
There are three phases in the gradle build, initialization, configuration and execution.
In gradle docs we can see:
Configuration During this phase the project objects are configured. The build scripts of all projects which are part of the build are executed.</description></item><item><title>How to use several git accounts in same computer</title><link>https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/blogpost2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 19:34:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://sergiobertolinsg.github.io/blog/posts/blogpost2/</guid><description>Sometimes we have the need of using several git accounts. We can be doing different projects, working for different companies, maybe using different collaborative version control tools and other reasons.
This leads to different problems. For example you make commits with the wrong account and forces you to amend them or you cannot interact with the tools because it needs different authentication.
To solve this we can make use of the git config possibilities.</description></item></channel></rss>